hot-web-ads.com 2010-12-31

# Hot-Web-Ads.com - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

General

Hot-Web-Ads.com takes your privacy seriously. We utilize safe, secure technology to protect your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy describes how Hot-Web-Ads.com treats the personal information that Hot-Web-Ads.com collects and receives through its website. Hot-Web-Ads.com values your trust in us and will work hard to earn your confidence, so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to family and friends.

Hot-Web-Ads.com reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will provide notice of any significant changes to this Privacy Policy, by posting such changes on the Hot-Web-Ads.com website. You may review a current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the Privacy Policy link at the bottom of any page of the site.

Information We Collect and How It Is Used

Like most standard web servers, our website uses log files to collect standard web log entries, including your IP address, page URL, browser type, platform type, and timestamp. We use this information to diagnose problems with our server, for the purposes of system administration, and to otherwise provide you with better services. 

Hot-Web-Ads.com collects personally information such as name, email address and contact phone number while you post ad using our website. Your name or ad owner name is required but other personal information is optional to input. Such information will be displayed when other users view your ad so that they can contact you if they are interested in your products or services. You may put your contact information inside your ad description. However, you understand that ad description and other contact information will be displayed on the website when other users view your ad details, and that Hot-Web-Ads.com website pages may be linked by third party websites or search engines. You agree that Hot-Web-Ads.com may send you email using your email address if provided when the users viewing your ad want to contact you by using our email system.

The users of our services may contact you by themselves via your email address and/or phone number if you provided in your posting. Hot-Web-Ads.com declines all responsibilities for such contact and all results caused by such contact.

If you contact us directly by sending email to any address at Hot-Web-Ads.com, or send comments through our website, your email address will be used if we reply to your comments or questions. 

Please do not post or submit any personal information that you expect to keep private. 

Protecting your Privacy

Hot-Web-Ads.com does not sell or rent your personal data to anyone. The personal data you provide us is saved in a secure environment and is kept in our records. Information collected is stored in a single, secure database, accessible only by Hot-Web-Ads.com. We employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies in order to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. Because this website is hosted by third party, we cannot guarantee complete security. 

Hot-Web-Ads.com, or users of Hot-Web-Ads.com, may provide links to third party websites. We are not responsible for, or have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites. We encourage all users to read the privacy policies of all websites visited. 

Use of Cookies

Hot-Web-Ads.com may set and access "cookies", small text files placed on your hard drive, to keep track of the pages visited. The "cookies" do not reveal personal information, rather give us statistical data to help analyze our web page flow and measure effectiveness. By tracking the overall traffic patterns of our visitors, we can make the site more responsive to our visitors' needs and interests. Using cookies is popular by many websites.

Third party websites made available by, or through, Hot-Web-Ads.com, may also assign cookies. Hot-Web-Ads.com does not control the use of cookies by third party websites, have any access to such cookies or to any information that they contain. 

Compliance with the Law

Hot-Web-Ads.com reserves the right to release information about its users in order to comply with the law. We may also release personal data to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our services, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Hot-Web-Ads.com, our users, or the general public. 

A Special Note about Children

Hot-Web-Ads.com does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 18. Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use Hot-Web-Ads.com website unsupervised. If you are under the age of 18, you may use Hot-Web-Ads.com website only in conjunction with and under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian. If Hot-Web-Ads.com learns that a posting has been submitted by a person under the age of 18 without supervised, we will remove that post. 

Should you have any questions, concerns, or comments, please **contact us**.

Hot-Web-Ads.com - 100% [Free Online Advertising](http://www.hot-web-ads.com/). No Sign up Required.
